Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1
- Box: 38, Folder: 2 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Item 25: Group Insurance Benefit, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
    By Coleman Company Inc. Februrary 1, 1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Pension Plan For Hourly and Weekly Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Item 27: The Sheldon Coleman Charitable and Educational Trust, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Item 28: A Summary of Your Coleman Benefit Plans, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Item 29: Educated Assistance Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Item 30: Manual of Rights and Responsibilities: Wichita Factory Employees, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
    By Coleman Company Inc. Revised July 1, 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Manual of Rights and Responsibilities: Wichita Factory Employees, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
    By Coleman Company Inc. Revised November, 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Coleman Spot-Lite, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
    By Coleman Company Inc. v.12:no.7 (1952:Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Coleman Company Inc. Employees Stock Purchase Plan Number Two, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Item 34: Group Insurance Protection, Publication (Box 38, Folder 2)
    By Coleman Company Inc. December 1, 1964. Item is in English.
- Box: 38, Folder: 3 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Business and Human Values, Publication (Box 38, Folder 3)
    By Albert L. Nickerson. Talk delivered at The College English Association Institute. Item is in English.
- Box: 38, Folder: 4 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Agreement for Operators between CBO Company and Evertt Refinery Represntation Association, Publication (Box 38, Folder 4)
    By General Office and Plant Clerical and Accounting Employees, Cafeteria Employees, Telephone Operators, Receptionists, Metal Inspectors, and Knock Engine Operators; Colonial Beacon Oil Company. Item is in English.
- Box: 38, Folder: 5 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Employees Hospital, Surgical and Medical Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
    By Colgate-Palmolive Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Agreement between Colgate-Palmolive-Peet Co. and Employees Association Inc., Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Sickness and Accident Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Agreement between Colgate-Palmolive Co. and Employees Association Inc., Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Sickness and Accident Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Employees Hospital, Surgical and Medical Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Agreement between Colgate-Palmolive-Peet Co. and Employees Association Inc., Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Agreement between Colgate-Palmolive Co. and Employees Association Inc., Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Agreement between Colgate-Palmolive Co. and Employees Association Inc., Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Employees Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Employees Hospital, Surgical and Medical Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: Employees Retirement Income Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: Employees Retirement Income Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: Colgate-Palmolive Company Employees Savings and Investment Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: A World of Opportunity with Colgate-Palmolive Company, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: Employees Savings and Investment Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 17: Sickness and Accident Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 18: Employees Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 19: Sickness and Accident Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 20: Employees Hospital, Surgial and Medial Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 21: Job Safety and Health Manual, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 22: Employees Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 23: Employees Retirement Income Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Item 24: Sickness and Accident Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Box: 38, Folder: 6 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Historical Review, Publication (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Employees Savings and Investment Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Book of Benefits for You and Your Family, Publication (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Box: 38, Folder: 7 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Colonial Transmitter: Special Television Edition, Publication (Box 38, Folder 7)
    By Colonial Radio Corporation. v.2:no.9 (1949:July 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: An Introduction to Colonial, Publication (Box 38, Folder 7)
    By Colonial Radio Corporation. Item is in English.
- Box: 38, Folder: 8 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Information Concerning Physical Examination of Applicants for Employment, Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    By Medical Department of CF&I Co. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Joint Representation of Employees and Management and Procedure in Industrial Relations and Memoranda Agreement, Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    By Colorado Fuel and Iron Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Information Concerning the Company's Labor Policies, Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Wage Readjustments in the Colorado Fuel and Iron Company During 1921, Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Disorders in Colorado, Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    By J.F. Welborn. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Industrial Bulletin; Minnequa Steel Works Beautifation Number, Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    By Colorado Fuel and Iron Company. v.7:no.5 (1922:Nov. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Industrial Bulletin; Progress in Beautification, Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    By Colorado Fuel and Iron Company. v.9:no.4 (1924:Oct. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Industrial Bulletin; Joint Representation Annual Review Number, Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    By Colorado Fuel and Iron Company. v.9:no.1 (1924:Feb. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Industrial Bulletin; Joint Representation, Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
    By Colorado Fuel and Iron Company. v.8:no.1 (1923:Jan. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Annual Report of the Sociological Department of CF&I Co., Publication (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Box: 38, Folder: 9 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Faculty Handbook, Publication (Box 38, Folder 9)
    By University of Colorado. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: You'll Enjoy Working With the University of Colorado, Publication (Box 38, Folder 9)
    By University of Colorado. Map. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Working with the University of Colorado; Staff Personnel Policies of the University of Colorado., Publication (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Staff Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Working with the University of Colorado; Staff Personnel Policies of the University of Colorado., Publication (Box 38, Folder 9)
    By University of Colorado. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Performance Rating; Personnel Form 14-66, Publication (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Box: 38, Folder: 10 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 38, Folder 10)
    By Colt Industries. Chandler Evans Control Systems Division. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Telephone Reference Investigation, Publication (Box 38, Folder 10)
    By Colt Industries. Blank personnel form. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Job Inquiry, Publication (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Interviewer's Guide, Publication (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Induction Interview Check List, Publication (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: General Introduction, Publication (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Monographs of Hartford Suburbs, Publication (Box 38, Folder 10)
    By Colt Industries. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Life Insurance Statement of Information, Publication (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Pension Plan for Exempt Salaried Personnel, Publication (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: Job Evaluation, Publication (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: Job Evaluation Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: Description of the Factors in the Various Grades, Publication (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: Employees Pension Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 10)
    By Colt's Manufacturing Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Employee Retirement Plan for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Item 15: General Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Item 16: Profit-Sharing Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Item 17: Group Accident Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Item 18: Colt's Employees Pension Plan for Eligible Employees, Publication (Box 38, Folder 10)
    By Colt's Manufacturing Company. Non- Contributory Plan for Hourly and Salaried Employees. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Chandler Evans Inc. Educational Refund Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Box: 38, Folder: 11 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Sales and profits of CBS, Publication (Box 38, Folder 11)
    By CBS (Columbia Broadcasting System). Press release. March 17, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: CBS Career Appraisal: A Handbook, Publication (Box 38, Folder 11)
    By CBS (Columbia Broadcasting System). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: CBS Management Education, Publication (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: CBS Memorandum, Publication (Box 38, Folder 11)
    By John D. Backe. October 30, 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: CBS Memorandum, Publication (Box 38, Folder 11)
    By Joan Showalter. November 21, 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Policy Notes from the President, Publication (Box 38, Folder 11)
    By John D. Backe. February 23, 1979. Item is in English.
- Box: 38, Folder: 12 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: A Case of Genuine Industrial Self Government, Publication (Box 38, Folder 12)
    By Paul H. Douglas. Reprinted from The University Journal, v.1:no.1 (1922:Nov.) and v.1:no.2 (1923:Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: An Experiment in Workers' Management and Ownership, Publication (Box 38, Folder 12)
    By The Columbia Conserve Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: An Experiment in Industrial Democracy, Publication (Box 38, Folder 12)
    By William P. Hapgood. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Supplement to "An Experiment in Workers' Management and Ownership", Publication (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: A Business Without A Boss, Publication (Box 38, Folder 12)
    By Boyd Gurley. Item is in English.
- Box: 38, Folder: 13 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Report of Meeting With Security Analysts, Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    By Columbia Gas System. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Application for Employment, Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    By Columbia Gas System. Blank personnel form. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: 7 reasons why Columbia Gas is a good place to work..., Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Our Company, Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: You and Columbia Gas System, Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: This is Our Company, Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Columbia Gas System, Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: Gasco News, Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    By Columbia Gas of Ohio. v.22:no.2 (1966:Summer). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Gasco News, Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
    By Columbia Gas of Ohio. v.22:no.1 (1966:Spring). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Annual Safety Report: Safety Committee, Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 11: Training Procedures and Procedures, Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 12: Treasury Training Program, Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 13: Comprehensive Medical Expense Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 14: Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 15: Employees' Thrift Plan of Columbia Gas System, Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 16: Retirement Income Plan For Columbia Gas System Companies, Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Item 17: Education Assistance Plan, Publication (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Box: 38, Folder: 14 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Training Program For Engineer Trainees, Publication (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Emloyee Safety Handbook, Publication (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: A History Of The Columbia Gas System, Publication (Box 38, Folder 14)
    By Columbia Gas System. Reprinted from ColumbiaToday. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Employee Orientation Program: Supervisor's Guide, Publication (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Box: 38, Folder: 15 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Employee Benefits Handbook, Publication (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Box: 38, Folder: 16 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Milepost, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
    By Columbia Gulf Transmission Company. v.5:no.8 (1959:Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: News and Views, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
    By Pittsburgh Group. v.24:no.3 (1959:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Pipeline, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
    By Charleston Group. v.11:no.3 (1959:Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Pipeline, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
    By Charleston Group. v.16:no.3 (1964:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: News and Views, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
    By Pittsburgh Group. v.29:no.3 (1964:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Gasco News, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
    By Columbia Group. v.20:no.2 (1964:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Gasco News, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
    By Columbia Group. v.16:no.3 (1959:July/Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Where We've Been: Where We're Going, Publication (Box 38, Folder 16)
    By Columbia Group. Item is in English.
- Box: 39, Folder: 1 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Courses in Personnel Management, Publication (Box 39, Folder 1)
    By Columbia University. 23 Sept - 1 Feb; 2 Feb - 28 May. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Human Resource Strategies and Competitiveness in the Textile and Apparel Industries, Publication (Box 39, Folder 1)
    By Conservation of Human Resources Project and The Center for Survey Research. Spring; 21 April; Draft. Item is in English.
- Box: 39, Folder: 2 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Industrial and Public Relations Program, Publication (Box 39, Folder 2)
    By Columbia Steel and Shafting Company. Item is in English.
- Box: 39, Folder: 3 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Columbian Rope: for Every Use, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
    By Columbian Rope Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Columbian Knot Chart, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
    By Colubia Rope Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Merit Rating Procedure and Employe Rating Report, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Merit Rating Procedure and Employe Rating Report, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Box: 39, Folder: 4 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Unemployment Insurance Legislation in 1964 (by States_, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
    By Social Insurance Department. 15 Vol., 17 No., 9 Dec. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Federal Unemployment Compensation Tax for 2964 - By States (Payable January, 1965), Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
    By Social Insurance Department. 15 Vol., 16 no., 17 Nov. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Amendments to the Social Security Act - Wages (Moving Expensives), Disability Provisions, etc., Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
    By Social Insurance Department. 15 Vol., 15 No., 11 Nov. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: A Proposal for a Permanent Program of Extended Unemployment Insurance Benefits, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
    By Social Insurance Department. 15 Vol., 14 No., 9 Nov. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Highlights of the 1964 Meeting of the Interstate Conference of Employment Security Agencies, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
    By Social Insurance Department. 15 Vol., 13 No., 28 Oct. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Average New York 1964 and 1963 UnemploymentInsurance Tax Rates by Detailed Industry Classification, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
    By Social Insurance Department. 15 Vol., 12 No., 21 Sept. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Voluntary Unemployment Insurance Contributions for Taxable Year 1965, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
    By Social Insurance Department. 15 Vol., 11 No., 6 Aug. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Average Employer Contribution Rates, by State, Calendar Years 1962-1964, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
    By Social Insurance Department. 15 Vol., 10 No., 1 July. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Governor's Committee to Study Hospital Costs and Alignment of State Responsibilities in the Hospital Field, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
    By Social Insurance Department. 15 Vol., 9 No., 15 June. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Unemployment Fund, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
    By Social Insurance Department. 15 Vol., 8 No., 3 June. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Total or Permanent Disability Under the Federal Social Security Act, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
    By Social Insurance Department. 15 Vol., 7 No., 21 May. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: 1964 Legislation of Medical Assistance to the Aged, etc., Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
    By Social Insurance Department. 15 Vol., 6 No., 4 May. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Hospital Cost - Legislative Action, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
    By Social Insurance Department. 15 Vol., 5 No., 1 May. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: 1964 Unemployment Insurance Laws, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
    By Social Insurance Department. 15 Vol., 4 No., 20 April. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: 1964 Amendments to the Disability Benefit Law, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
    By Social Insurance Department. 15 Vol., 3 No., 15 April. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Unemployment Insurance Tax Formula, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
    By Social Insurance Department. 15 Vol., 2 No., 11 Feb. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Support Amendments to Disability Benefit Law, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
    By Social Insurance Department. 15 Vol., 1 No., 10 Feb. Item is in English.
- Box: 39, Folder: 5 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: New York City's Annual Briefing Session on Collective Bargaining 1965, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    By Commerce and Inudstry Association of New York, Inc. 2 March; Waldor-Astoria Hotel. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: 1945 New Yorck City Manual of Clerical Salary Rates and Practices including Annaul Clerical Salary Survey 1944, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    By Commerce and Inudstry Association of New York, Inc. 26 June. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Letter to Personnel Officers of Member Firms, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    By Thomas Jefferson Miley. 17 Dec. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Report to Members Years Ending April 20, 1950 - Association Action, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    By Commerce and Inudstry Association of New York, Inc. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: News, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    By Commerce and Inudstry Association of New York, Inc. No. 7, 7 Feb. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Letter to Personnel Officers of Member Firms, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    By Thomas Jefferson Miley. 26 November. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Be Ready of the Job You Want, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Bulletin, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    By Commerce and Inudstry Association of New York, Inc. 16 Vol., 35 No., 19 Oct. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Bulletin, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    By Commerce and Inudstry Association of New York, Inc. 17 Vol., 2 No., 11 Jan. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Letter to the Members of the Commerce and Industry Association of New York, Inc., Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    By Ralph G. Risley. 9 Oct. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Workshops on High School and College Recruiting, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    By Ralph C. Gross. 16 Feb; Memo to Employment Managers, Personnel Officers. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Workshop on Perspectives on Mental Health and Workshop on Contract Administration and Grievance Handling, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    By Bryant S. Stokes. 11 Oct; Memo to Personnel and Labor Relations Officers. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Survey of Pay Policy and Fringe Benefits for Men Placed on Active military Duty, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    By Peter J. Lynch and Survey Division of Industrial Relations Department. 20 Sept; Letter from Lynch attached. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Workshop on "Teamster Problems and Contract Negotiations", Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    By Commerce and Inudstry Association of New York, Inc. 15 Nov; Memo to Industrial Managers and Trucking Supervisors. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Workshop Preview, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    By Commerce and Inudstry Institute, Inc. January - March. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Guidelines in Discrimination Because or Religion, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    By Industrial Relations Department. 17 Vol., 13 No., 20 June. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Enacted State Labor Legislation - 1965, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    By Industrial Relations Department. 16 Vol., 18 No., 5 Aug. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Cumulative Index of Personnel Mangement Bulletin, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    By Industrial Relations Department. 16 Vol., 25 No., 30 Dec. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Year-End Holiday Practices - 1965, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    By Industrial Relations Department. 16 Vol., 24 No., 8 Dec. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Guidelines on Sex Discrimination Provisions of Title VII of Civil Rights At of 1964, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    By Industrial Relations Department. 16 Vol., 23 No., 2 Dec. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Fair Labor Standards Act Sets Guides for Holiday Employment of Youth, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    By Industrial Relations Department. 16 Vol., 22 No., 24 Nov. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Reorganization of Federal Civil Rights Functions, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    By Industrial Relations Department. 16 Vol., 21 no., 19 Oct. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Discrimination Because of Sex - New York State Law, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    By Industrial Relations Department. 16 Vol., 20 No., 27 Sept. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Flu Shots - 1965, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    By Industrial Relations Department. 16 Vol., 19 No., 11 Aug. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Procedures of the Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    By Industrial Relations Department. 16 Vol/. 17 no., 22 July. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Youth Opportunity Campaign - A Statement by President Johnson, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    By Industrial Relations Department. 16 Vol, 16 no., 14 July. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Report on Extending Private Pension Coverage, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    By Industrial Relations Department. 16 Vol., 14 No., 24 June. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Driver Salesmen - Proposed Revision of Regulation, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    By Industrial Relations Department. 16 Vol., 15 No., 7 July. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: New York City's Annual Briefing Session On Collectiove Bargaining, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    By Bureau of National Affairs. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Personnel Management, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    By Commerce & Industry Association of New York, Inc. Vol. 16-No.15. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Personnel Management, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    By Commerce & Industry Association of New York, Inc. Vol.16-No.12. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Personnel Management, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)